&GT；&GT；Kyle Simpson：现在我总是从人们那里得到的论点，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Now the argument I always get back from people,
你们中的一些人可能会认为现在这个是，是的，
and some of you may be thinking this at this moment is, yeah,
但即使我坐在你的工作室里学到了所有这些细微的差别
but even if I sat through your workshop and I learned all these nuances and
我读了规范，那么我代码库上所有的初级开发人员呢？
I read the spec, what about all the junior devs on my code base?
他们永远不会理解这些东西。
They would never understand this stuff.
实际上，从理论上讲，这个问题几乎比我收到的任何问题都更让我震惊。
This I actually, in theory, hits me almost more than any question I ever get.
这种心态说，好吧，我够聪明，但是
This mindset that says, well I'm smart enough but
那些年轻的开发人员，他们太笨了，不能理解这些东西。
those junior devs they're too dumb to understand this stuff.
这完全是胡说八道。
That is complete and total nonsense.
我不知道你的背景是什么，但是
I don't know what your backgrounds are, but
你们每个人都很擅长自己的工作。
everyone of you is excellent at what you do.
您可能或多或少了解JavaScript，但这并不会让您变得更笨
You may know more or less about JavaScript but that doesn't make you dumber and
理解事物的能力较弱，学习事物的能力较弱。
less capable of understanding stuff, less capable of learning things.
我不同意我们应该
I do not subscribe to the belief that we should
将我们的代码基础降低到最低公分母。
dumb down our code basis to the lowest common denominator.
你绝对应该尽可能有效地使用这些工具。
You should absolutely use the tools as effectively as you can.
你应该尽可能清楚你是如何使用这些工具的。
You should be as obvious about how you're using the tools as possible.
当有人在代码基础上不理解的时候，
And when somebody is on the code base who doesn't understand,
利用它作为他们学习的机会。
use it as an opportunity for them to learn.
使用代码评审，
Use code reviews,
使用点对点学习的文化，结对在一起。
use a culture of peer-to-peer learning, of pairing together.
所有这些都可以帮助每个人了解该工具如何更好地工作。
All of those things to help everybody learn how the tool works better.
当您收到代码审查时，一些初级开发人员做了一些愚蠢的事情，
When you receive a code review and some junior developer did something dumb,
就像他们没有做正确的强制，也许有一些角落的情况，他们没有
like they didn't do a coercion correct and maybe there's some corner case they didn't
知道，你不会拒绝代码审查并说，你很笨。
know about, you don't reject the code review and say, you're dumb.
你说，嘿，过来和我坐一会儿，
You say, hey, come sit with me for a minute,
让我跟你谈谈你不知道的那个角落里的案子，而且
let me just talk to you about this corner case that you weren't aware of, and
如果你做这件事，我们会完全避免那个角落的情况。
if you did this thing instead we'd avoid that corner case entirely.
现在你学得更好了，他们学得也更好了。
Now you learned better and they learned better.
这是一个彻头彻尾的胡说八道，这是一个懒惰的借口
This is a complete bunk argument, it's a lazy excuse for
不想在我们的开发团队中真正做我们应该做的事情，这就是
not wanting to actually do what we ought to do on our developer teams, which is
提倡每个人都应该学习，每个人都应该向上。
promote that everybody should be learning, everybody should be headed upward.
我不在乎你在哪里，我在乎你的方向是什么，你是在往上走吗？
I don't care where you are, I care what your direction is, are you headed upward?
您正在了解有关工具的更多信息吗？
Are you learning more about your tool?
这不是不能很好地使用工具的借口。
This is not an excuse for not using the tools well.
这也不是聪明的借口，对吧。
It is also not an excuse for being clever, right.
有人说，这里的滑坡论。
Some people say, well the slippery slope argument here.
我可以做所有这些聪明的小数学，对吧。
I can do all this clever bit-wise math, right.
我在使用这个工具，我很聪明，我正在做所有的事情
I'm using the tool and I'm being clever, and I'm doing all of
我在一行代码上进行编程，就像我们以前在Perl中所做的那样。
my programming on one line of code, the way we used to do in Perl.
我也不是这个意思。
That's not what I'm saying, either.
我实际上想说的是，您的代码是一种通信形式，并且
What I'm actually saying is that your code is a form of communication, and
有一种有效的沟通方式可以很好地理解和使用工具。
there is an effective way to communicate that understands and uses the tool well.
如果您要求代码的读者了解有关工具的一些内容，那么
If you ask the reader of a code to understand something about the tool so
他们能够理解这行代码，这是他们的一项投资。
that they can understand that line of code, that is an investment on their part.
确保投资的回报超出了这一行代码。
Make sure that that investment pays off beyond that line of code.
确保当他们知道这是如何工作的，他们会看到更多的。
Make sure that when they learn how that worked, they're gonna see more of that.
而不是，他们知道你是如何做一些奇怪的事情，
Rather than, they learn how you did something weird,
深奥的比特把戏，然后他们再也不会使用它了。
esoteric bitwise trick, and then they never get to use that ever again.
那是浪费他们的时间。
That's a waste of their time.
让你感觉很好，但这是浪费时间。
Makes you feel good but it's a waste of the time.
这也是我们为拥有良好的开发文化而努力奋斗的部分原因，
And it's part of the reason why we struggle so much to have good dev culture,
因为我们并不是专注于推广每个人都应该能够理解的东西。
cuz we're not focused on promoting that everybody should be able to understand.
从学习JavaScript三周的人到一直在做这件事的人
From the person who is three weeks into JavaScript to somebody who's been at it
像我这样20多年来，
for 20 plus years like me,
我们都应该能够在相同的代码库上进行互操作，并且能够很好地沟通。
we all oughta be able to interoperate on the same code base and communicate well.
是的，初级开发人员需要学习一些东西，但这就是发生在
Yeah, the junior devs gonna need to learn some stuff, but that's what happens in
每一份工作，每一个行业，你都必须学习一些东西。
every job and in every industry, you have to learn some stuff.
你看不到建筑师说，
You don't see an architect saying,
嗯，我们不会设计好那栋楼，因为我们有一个实习生在工作。
well we're not gonna design that building well cuz we've got an intern on the job.
你教实习生如何建好大楼。
You teach the intern how to build the building well.
这就是我们需要做的。
That's what we need to be doing.
我们需要处理JavaScript的所有部分，但是
We need to be doing with all parts of JavaScript, but
特别是那些每个人都告诉你要忽略的部分，比如类型。
especially the parts that everybody tells you to ignore like types.